Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Are you okay?
I thought I would never see you again.
Relax.
I'm here.
I will never let anything happen to you.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Qi Miao.
There's something I want to tell you.
I finally understand my feelings.
I like you.
I want to be with you.
Forever.
It's not because of the connection.
It's because, for the first time,
I've felt something different for someone.
And that feeling—
it's love.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
Just overused my energy, that's all.
Are you crazy?
Because of that kiss with you earlier,
my crystal recharged its energy.
She's so beautiful.
And—
she's so gentle.
Whose bratty kid is this?
Go play somewhere else.
Let's go.
Even when she's working seriously,
she's stunning.
So they were chatting all along.
Oh my gosh.
What's going on?
Ai Yite.
I'm so happy right now!
My dear son has finally found someone!
Qi Miao and Hao Ruichi are together now!
See? I told you.
When you like someone,
you need to bravely confess your feelings.
Anyway, I'm off.
I need to make them a love-filled dinner.
She actually hugged me!
Could it be that she likes me too?
Even someone as dense as Hao Ruichi
managed to confess successfully.
I can definitely do it too!
Come over and help me!
Piece of cake.
I have something to tell you.
What is it? Spill it.
I...
Actually...
Oh come on, stop being so hesitant.
Just say it if you have something to say.
I want to say...
Are you going to say it or not?
From the moment I first met you,
I deeply fell in love with you.
Will you be my girlfriend?
No, no!
Aren’t we just like brothers?
I’ve never thought about this at all.
Aiyet,
Drink up!
Don’t drink too much.
If you overdo it,
it might make you lose your memory.
Stop nagging!
Drink!
Hao Ruichi,
aren’t we Blue Star people supposed to be really lucky?
Why am I so unlucky?
From being chased off Blue Star by you,
to barely escaping here,
and almost losing my life.
All these years,
this is the first time I’ve liked a girl.
And she just wants to be my brother?
Who wants to just be her brother?
I like her so much!
Why doesn’t she like me back?
Why, Hao Ruichi?
If she doesn’t like me,
then what’s the point of me staying here?
What meaning does it have?
Hao Ruichi,
take me away from here.
Hao Ruichi
Take me with you
Bring me along
I’m not leaving anymore
Hao Ruichi
What… what did you say?
I said I want to stay here
I’m not leaving
So
Eytet is also someone from your place?
He’s the one I’ve been looking for
No wonder you two know each other
Then
When you find him, are you going to take him back?
That was the plan
But
Now I’ve fallen for someone
Because of her
I don’t want to leave anymore
Qi Miao
I’m staying
That’s wonderful, Hao Ruichi
Wait a second
What’s this?
I found this online
A list of little things to do when you’re in love
A hundred wishes I want to fulfill with you
Our first hug
Our first
Why are there two question marks here?
That’s something not convenient to write down
Why?
Because
Last time
You got upset over this
It’s a kiss, silly
Dummy
But it’s different now
Come here
Hey!
Alright, alright
Bye-bye
Let’s go camping tomorrow
Sure
So,
is this considered our first date?
Of course.
Qi Miao,
are you ready?
I’m ready.
What’s wrong?
Do I look bad?
You look amazing.
Miss Qi,
may I kiss you?
Sis, are you guys ready yet?
Sorry.
You two carry on.
I'll wait for you outside.
Wasn't this supposed to be just a date between the two of us?
He was free today,
so I invited him along.
Let’s go.
Report, Goddess!
We’ve detected Hao Ruichi’s energy traces.
Find him as soon as possible!
Understood!
Hao Ruichi,
don’t die too soon.
If you're going to die,
it has to be at my hands.